HERCULES REVENGE
Hercules at once, man and god,
knows no limit to his power.
To punish him for his audacity
the Gods of Olympus have condemned him
to accomplish 12 superhuman tasks,
of which the last is the most dreadful,
defeating Cerberus,
the monstrous guardian of Hell
and penetrating the Kingdom of Shades,
from which no living being
has ever returned alive.
His friends already weep for Hercules,
whilst his enemies, the fiercest
being Eurito, cruel tyrant of ECCALIA,
were preparing to share his spoils.
Hercules won't return to the Earth.
None of those who descend to
the Kingdom of the Dead ever come back.
No. He won't come back.
And Thebes without Hercules is nothing.
My friends, I tell you,
Thebes will fall at our first assault.
Aristeo, don't you agree?
Mighty Eurito,
we have always been your allies
and have always followed your advice.
- But...
- Quiet!
And you?
- If Hercules is really dead...
- If... if... if!
I didn't gather you together
to hear your fears and doubts.
I wanted to know if you were
ready to help me conquer Thebes.
You want a sincere answer
from your allies?
But the walls of Megara are not
as inviolable as those of your city..
The city walls were
built by mere mortals.
- And we'll be exposed to the vengeance of Hercules.
- Hercules, Hercules...
You're frightened of his name
even though he's dead.
Hercules is dead and won't return.
And you to be safe
need Thebes to be destroyed.
Hurry if you want to leave.
Eurito, I ask you just to let me think.
- Tomorrow, you will have my answer.
- And mine.
Very well, I'll wait till tomorrow,
but no longer.
But I won't see your faces
covered in fear.
- Thea.
- Illo.
I tremble with joy.
And I shudder with horror.
- Danger won't stop the son of Hercules.
- Why are we forced to meet in secret?
Love is not a crime.
Hercules has forbidden me
to come to Ecalia.
He wouldn't tell me the reason.
Even Eurito is against our marriage.
I'm worried by all the risks you run.
If you wish I will follow you anywhere.
- Yes Thea, let's leave this night.
- No, darling.
Tonight is not possible.
The city is full of soldiers.
I'll let you know the right time.
I have your promise, remember.
And this cameo
is the pledge of our love.
When the time comes, send for me.
I'll know it's the signal
and run to you.
- I'm tired of this suffering.
- There's no need, Ismene.
See how your loved one is happy,
celebrating the victory he's yet to win.
The one I love loves me no more.
Go to Thea, but don't arouse
the suspicions of the two lovebirds.
You will always be
my evil genius, Tindaro.
If it wasn't for Eurito,
I swear to you...
When I think of Thea.
The child I've seen grow.
And what makes me sick
is that she still has faith in me.
Fine feelings are no longer in order.
Go!
Good food and good wine
promote the right decisions.
You can be sure.
You have in us, faithfully allies.
- Quick, the guards arrive...
- Go, I beg you.
Remember your signal.
Come, come, my Thea.
You know I'm your friend.
If Eurito knew I'd helped you,
he'd never forgive me.
Help me Ismene.
If you could change Eurito's mind.
Perhaps Illo could obtain
the consent of his father.
There's nothing to say.
Your father can't help you now.
Leave him to calm down.
Tomorrow he may be more reasonable.
Your hospitality, great Eurito
shows your great power
of course, it is.
My friends, before you commit
to the fight against Thebes
I will prove that Hercules
is dead.
I am so sure that Hercules is dead
that I'll give you tomorrow
the spectacle of the execution
of his son Illo.
You dare do that?
The Gods have dared kill the father.
I dare to kill the son.
- After which we will take Thebes.
- If this is so, Mycenas will be with you.
- Also Pillo.
- Medea too.
And Macedonia too.
You stay silent Thymocles?
I was counting on you.
You're right,
but I must be getting old.
And old age is slow
in deed as well as in decision.
You know Alcinoe?
Her father was old
and often indecisive like you.
I burnt his city and killed him.
Now his daughter is my slave.
As a token of my friendship.
A small image of the mighty Thebes.
A city which has grown too large,
and which we all covet.
Is it not so?
- Thebes...
- The object of your desires, and mine.
I fear that this gift is a weight
a little too heavy for my weak forces.
The idea of razing Thebes is attractive
But...
Alcinoe... If you wish
you need only say one word
to regain your freedom.
I prefer to be the slave of Eurito
At least I can hate him.
For you I have nothing but contempt.
Together our forces can bring about
the end of the Theban cavalry.
Perhaps you're right. Nobody can
come back from the Kingdom of the Dead.
- Not even Hercules.
- Finally, nothing can stop us.
Themocles?
Messenger, what news do you bring?
From Megara?
No, from the Kingdom of the Dead.
- Hercules?
- I've just learnt what all Greece will know shortly.
Hercules defeated the invincible and heads
for the temple of the God of Vengeance.
To offer the cyclopean diamond
which has stolen the infernal powers.
Cowards! Away!
I don't want, I've no need of you.
Tomorrow, before my people
I will execute Illo.
The world will know
that I challenge Hercules.
Relax, Eurito.
Tomorrow you will execute no one.
- Listen, tonight Illo will escape.
- Are you as afraid as the others?
No, Eurito.
Only, I have a brain.
I know how to think.
- You are only a mass of muscle, of violence, a beast.
- Enough!
And what would you do?
I'm listening.
What would you do?
Tell me Eurito,
what determines the actions of men?
- Destiny.
- No, it's not destiny,
but self interest.
Take the example of Illo,
This young man wants to Thea.
And to have her,
he'd do anything.
And Alcinoe, what does she want?
Alcinoe wants her freedom.
If you want to follow my advice
then call Alcinoe.
- Who are you?
- Speak softly, I'm Alcinoe.
I've come to help you escape.
The guards won't intervene.
Why do this?
Because Thea is the only one here
who's been good to me.
And also because
Ismene wants your freedom.
Eurito had forbidden Thea to see you.
Thea... But why?
To assure the friendship of Hercules
and to have a free hand against Thebes.
But Hercules asked for a condition.
He wants Thea.
- You lie!
- Haven't I proved the opposite?
Please forgive me.
- Thea is young, she's beautiful.
- Swear to me you speak the truth.
- I swear by Zeus I will find my father.
- You'll do nothing.
Don't speak to your father or anyone.
And don't set foot in the palace.
- But...
- If you love Thea, listen
I will tell what to do
when the time comes.
Go now, it's dawn.
You must hurry!
God of vengeance,
now your rage against me is placated.
By the sign of this gem,
which I bring you,
and which has the colour of blood.
Hercules.
You have completed
the last of the twelve tasks.
Now finally...
- Repeat those wonderful words.
- Yes, Hercules, you are free.
The Gods will impose no more tasks.
Now you can live in peace.
I've long dreamed of peace,
to live as other men.
- So that my peace can be complete, answer me one thing.
- Speak.
My son and Thea.
Hercules, my friend!
Let me be the first to embrace you.
All Thebes offered prayers
for your victory.
And I needed them.
Death was never so close.
Let me accompany you.
To see the joy of your wife and son.
And you, noble knights return to Thebes
and dispel the last fears.
Tell everyone you have seen Hercules,
alive and victorious.
Return to my house,
to rest and live in peace.
You can't imagine
what this return means to me.
Even heroes need to rest.
Now you'll be able to relax.
Now it's done, My Lady.
I've prepared the room for Hercules and
burnt perfumes to assure him sweet dreams.
Good.
Down from there!
I'll prepare a Cretan boar,
the preferred dish of Hercules.
Bravo, we must celebrate
the return of the Master.
What is the reason for sadness, Illo?
I never heard you play like today.
And today's the return of your father.
What is the reason for your torment?
Thea?
Yes I suffer.
But I cannot tell you why.
I don't want that my suffering
should cause you suffering too.
What suffering is grater than
seeing a son suffer
without being able to help?
- You know my father is hostile to Thea.
- But that's because of Eurito.
But that's not the only reason, Mother.
There's another.
That he hides from me as from you.
My father wants the girl for himself!
How dare you? Your father...
It's not possible.
It was revealed to me
by someone who has no reason to lie.
Maybe it would be better if my father
had never come back from the dead!
Don't say such a thing.?
Your father couldn't be your rival.
- I don't believe you.
- It's the truth.
Soon Hercules will be here.
You can put him to the test.
Ask him.
No, son, it's useless.
I have no need to question him.
- I know his heart like my own.
- Rather the truth frightens you!
- You prefer silence, and you know it!
- Enough! Stop it!
How dare you say that.
We're almost there.
Come on.
Almost.. You got it...
Without me you're good for nothing.
Look, it's Hercules!
Master, Master!
Hercules...
we need you.. Hercules.
Welcome back Master!
How was it in the underworld?
I was going to meet you.
But had to give these a hand.
And I had the idea
that you'd like to help us.
- If you'd like some help.
- Why not.
Ready?
See... because of me, you had done it
Hercules has done it.
Thank you, Hercules.
May the gods protect you.
Wait. Wait for me.
Hercules.
- Hercules, welcome back.
- How are you?
- I'm clearing the ground.
- Excellent idea!
- I've bought a pair of oxen, but you know...
- What?
They are rather weak and
I cannot get them to uproot the tree.
- There's nothing to be done.
- I understand. Come on.
Hercules - So good to see you.
Thank you, Hercules.
Do you need a hand, boss?
Let me...
Clear off, I told you.
Hercules!
- We've been waiting since this morning.
- Tell us how you killed Cerberus!
At last, how I've missed you.
Is it true it had a tongue of fire?
Don't you know
it's a monster with three heads!
- Don't bother the master.
- But I want to know what happened.
Tomorrow I'll tell you
how I killed the dragon.
- You take this!
- I wish I had a father like him.
Enough! Come on.
Where is Illo?
There he is.
Why didn't you come
to greet your father?
Taming your son,
that will be your last task.
Welcome, father.
When you greet me,
turn your head and look at me?
You must be hungry. And you too.
Everything is ready.
Sorry, tonight I want to be alone.
Don't worry, I'll stay with Illo.
Rest well.
Tomorrow we'll go hunting.
And talk of many things.
What is it with your father?
You can tell me what's on your mind.
I have nothing to say.
Aren't you eating?
Alright, I'm starving!
I'd be happy to accompany you.
- As you wish...
- Let's go.
He's jealous.
He wants your caresses...
- Try to sleep. Close your eyes.
- I don't want to sleep.
If I sleep I'll dream
of all those I've killed.
But now it's all over.
Now you're with me.
Nothing can trouble our peace.
Peace, even in the heart
of my family I can't find peace.
Did you see how Illo looked at me?
Just like an enemy.
Don't think of Illo.
He's still a child. He's in love.
- If you would consent to his love...
- Enough, I'll hear no more of it!
But why? Tell me the reason.
- He's always been in love with Thea...
- Enough, I said!
Speak not of that love.
I'd rather him dead than marry Thea.
And this is the filtre to give to Illo
to soften the heart of Hercules,
when you have gained their confidence
and present yourself as their saviour.
So you want to use me
to kill Hercules?
Only to make him see reason.
Is this also the poison that you used
to remove your friend Cleone,
the true King of Ecalia?
- You told her? - No, Eurito.
- You told me so in your sleep.
When you meet
the ghosts of your victims.
- What else have I said?
- You are frightened of losing power.
That you want to marry Thea,
daughter of the true king.
- And?
- That you are afraid of Hercules.
Did I also say
that I would kill you?
So I cannot give the poison to Illo.
And Hercules will live.
Alcinoe is right. We need her
and she can make her conditions.
- I've already promised her freedom.
- If I've understood correctly,
it seems to me that
Alcinoe's liberty wouldn't be enough.
Eurito, you have destroyed my
father's kingdom and made me a slave.
I want to be Queen.
There, on the throne, by your side.
- And if I say no?
- Why not, Eurito?
Alcinoe has always been your favourite.
Thea is so young, unimportant.
But Thea had the rights to the throne.
Poor Thea. So alone and
distraught at the death of her father.
We mustn't be cruel. Let's not separate
a loyal daughter from her parent.
And we can arrange that.
To reunite Thea with her father
would be something to please the Gods.
- You are crazy, Tindaro.
- Listen to me, Eurito.
Alcinoe will help us.
And we must reward her.
Don't I always offer good advice?
Alcinoe, you have his word.
Soon you will be queen.
I want to hear it
from his own mouth.
You have my word, Alcinoe.
Now go.
The escort is waiting for you to leave.
- And now?
- You can always take back your word.
I won't renounce Alcinoe
And you have need of Thea.
- And if she reveals our secret?
- She won't talk.
How do you know?
I know how to keep her quiet.
Here we are. Beyond the forest
is the house of Hercules.
- Everything depends on you.
- Don't worry. I know what I must do.
Wait here and hide yourselves.
Help me, oh Gods.
My heart trembles with fear..
Listen to my prayers. Protect my love
and soften his father, Hercules.
You're very lucky,
not even a scratch.
I arrived just in time. It would
have been a sin, a face like yours.
I hope fear hasn't left you mute.
Say something.
You have saved my life.
If not, I'd never
have forgiven myself.
I've hunted that bear
since this morning.
It's wild and ferocious
But why are you alone in the forest?
- Please don't ask me.
- Tell me at least your name.
- My name is Alcinoe. And who are you?
- I'm Hercules of Thebes.
Don't say my name frightens you?
Here are my companions.
Go on, away!
Hercules, at last.
Where were you hiding?
Oh, you've killed the bear.
I arrived just in time to save
Alcinoe from that wild beast.
Alcinoe? Who is Alcinoe?
There she.
I don't understand. But...
She was here just now.
It looks like she's made a fool of you.
Come on, Hercules.
You have given the phial to Illo,
to change his father's mind?
- I told you, Eurito.
- And you're sure nobody saw you?
- No one..
- Liar. We saw you.
You should have entrusted me.
I have always been loyal.
Yet you preferred that slave!
One who hates you,
rather than loves.
Enough sister. Now's not
the time to talk of love and hate.
- She carried out my orders.
- That's not true!
- Tell the truth.
- Alcinoe!
I'll answer for her.
She's betrayed me. Guards!
Take away that slave!
Faster!
No, more slowly!
You wil see.
I'm very happy to be back home
and find peace with my loved ones.
- May the gods protect you.
- We're happy to have you back with us.
- We have prayed for your success.
- Thank you dear friends.
- I'm not in the mood to celebrate.
- Your father will be unhappy.
Nothing can upset my father today.
- So you'll return to Ecalia?
- I've no other choice?
You've seen Hercules too,
will never change his mind.
I can only try to convince Eurito.
Come, Illo, eat.
- Farewell.
- May the gods protect you, my son.
It was the most difficult of my tasks
and now it's over I want to forget it.
And Illo? Where is Illo?
He has gone?
Gone where?
Hercules
Hercules, listen to me.
I know your heart is pure.
I don't know why you're like this, but
don't stop Illo from finding his love.
I'll tie you up unless you promise me
you'll not go near Ecalia,
- No!
- As you wish.
I've told you a thousand times,
I love Thea and you can't stop me.
I'm sorry son,
but it's for your own good.
I'm frightened, Androcles.
I'm afraid.
Have you seen. As soon as one mentions
Thea, you can't reason with him.
He seems out of his mind.
When you change your mind,
let me know and I'll set you free.
Excuse me, friends.
Now's the time to eat and be merry.
- And Illo?
- Relax, he's thinking it over.
- But Hercules...
- He'll be fine.
- But if he's hungry?
- Then he'll call.
Don't be afraid, Illo.
I'm Iris, the slave of Thea.
- Recognise it?
- It's from Thea.
She's in danger.
I must go to her aid.
- No, at Ecalia you can do nothing for her.
- Then what can I do?
- Confront your father and obtain his consent.
- It's impossible.
- My father is crazy.
- But you can change that.
- I prefer to be open with my father.
- Hurry, there's little time.
Father!
Father, untie me.
You've my word..
You see? The rope works wonders.
I'd like to join in your feast.
And drink a toast
to your triumphal return.
Finally I recognise my son!
Hey, look!
Alright.
Go, but hurry.
Illo is in danger.
He thinks Hercules is mad about you.
Yes, I know.
But Hercules will soon be cured.
Illo will give him a filtre
which will return his reason.
You have been tricked, Thea.
That filtre is poison.
It's a trap of Eurito's,
helped by lsmene.
- How is it possible?
- Yes, Thea.
- Ismene? Poison?
- It's the truth.
The poison will kill Hercules,
like it killed your father.
- My father?
- Your father didn't die like they wanted you to believe.
You can't marry Illo,
because Eurito wants you.
To legitimize his reign of terror.
It's true.
Get him.
So this is how
you use my presents, Alcinoe?
Take the others!
Now you'll see how I deal with traitors.
Your friends are in good hands.
Take it back.
- Assassin! You killed my father!
- Silence!
Mercy, please.
I see that you've told Thea
all my secrets
you will be treated same
as your accomplices.
You are lucky. Tindaro wants
you alive and I've promised him.
But you can stay here.
I don't want you running around.
You might get into trouble.
Understand?
That's enough.
We'll continue tomorrow.
Don't cry, Thea.
Our fate is sealed.
My fate is irrelevant, but Illo
received the poison from my own hands.
It was I who gave to Ismene
the pledge of love agreed between us.
Only a God could save us now.
The god Echo! Who carried
my words to Illo on the winds.
Dear friends, let's drink
to the health of the noble Hercules!
Protector of the humble, friend
of the honest, defender of our liberty!
Enemy of the tyrant of Ecalia.
Whilst Hercules lives, we'll all live.
Long live Thebes!
Long life to Hercules! And may
he find here among his friends,
and the sweet intimacy of his family
the peace and serene joy
which we all wish him!
Illo, stop!
If you love me, stop?
Stop! Stop!
I have been tricked.
I have been tricked, Illo.
The filtre is poison.
The filtre is poison. A poison!
Destroy it, Illo! Destroy it.
Destroy it, Illo!
Destroy it!
- But why? Why?
- Forgive me, father.
Forgive me.
Now, let's drink.
Let's drink.
Long live to Hercules!
- Won't you drink?
- Yes, father.
- Long live to Hercules!
Forgive me
stop.. Stop.
I don't ask for much, Hercules.
Only to return to Thebes.
It's always the same...
"I don't ask for much".
You know I'm tired of that life.
I've promised myself to live in peace.
I know, Hercules,
but Thebes is your city.
I'll attend the Council of Elders
but otherwise, do not count on me.
Of course, Hercules, you're right.
Your happiness means as much
to me as the safety of Thebes.
You have a way with words.
- Lika, my horse!
- It's already saddled, Master.
You knew I'd let myself be persuaded?
- Hercules, I have something to tell you.
- Illo?
- He's gone.
- And you let him?
He was desperate.
He threatened to kill himself.
Fool, Do you know what you've done?
Let me go.
Illo!
You, my advisor, my brain.
A great intriguer who
lets himself be fooled by a woman.
- A mere lad has upset your plans.
- I don't understand.
You understand nothing!
You who persuade me that
our actions are not governed by fate.
The fate that brought us Illo
despite your maneuvers.
I'll decide now as I should have
done from the beginning.
Illo will die.
So will I defy Hercules.
Here are all our allies,
except Timocles.
The worse for him. If he betrays our
alliance, his city will be destroyed.
I don't deserve this.
Don't do that, Hercules.
I have never been an ally of Eurito.
No I don't deserve this!
Be careful Hercules.
What does it mean, an elephant here?
- I don't understand, Eurito...
- You'll see in a moment.
I offer a spectacle
like you've never seen.
- My orders were carried out as I said?
- Don't worry, I checked personally.
The gates of Ecalia
are well guarded.
Soon it will be
the turn of the son of Hercules.
It's a great idea that elephant.
What a spectacle.
As you see, you're not
the only on to have ideas.
You want proof
that I'm not afraid of Hercules.
There, look at his son.
Now Ilo is going to die.
Ilo.
- There is someone at the gate!
- Stop. Let's wait a moment.
Stop! Wait for the order!
Wait!
Wait. Perhaps this time
Hercules will not be the stronger.
Get them!
Come on!
Approach and listen.
The oracle will reveal
what you must know.
Sibyl, Hercules invokes you.
You divine Prophetess,
who knows the future...
Reveal to my son,
the hidden truth.
Speak.
Ask me and I will answer you, Hercules.
Once I asked about Thea.
And you remained silent.
But now I beg you.
Reveal to my son your prophecy.
One day your descendants
will reign over Ecalia,
but it will cost the life
of the woman who is dearest to you.
Let's go, Illo.
Now you know the truth.
Your mother's life is in your hands.
- And Thea, father?
- You must forget her.
Yes, father.
But there is only one way!
Cursed be the day
that I built this house,
and cursed be this lying earth
which should have brought me peace.
No, Mistress. Leave him.
No one can appease his rage.
Collapse like my dreams!
We'll search for a more benign land
under more serene skies,
and there we'll build our new house,
as you see, and be happy.
Illo told me of the prophecy.
No one can escape their destiny.
Me, yes,
I'll fight it to the end.
I have good news.
Hercules and Illo are on the run.
Thea, I'm sorry
to have left you for so long confined.
But now it is over. And soon,
very soon, you will be queen.
No! I will never marry
the man who killed my father.
No.
- Stop it, Eurito.
- I know what I'm doing.
Look
what do you see?
No... no.. No.
Enough!
Keep out of this, Tindaro.
Well, have you decided?
- You condemn her to a terrible death.
- Tell me what you want.
Even to be your wife.
Enough, spare Alcinoe.
Master we can't cross.
There's water everywhere.
If we really want, we'll find a way.
But I can't swim!
We'll manage.
Come with me, let's see.
Mother, you alone know my pain.
Free me.
- What will you do?
- Let me fulfill my destiny.
Have pity on me.
You break my heart.
Free me if it's true that you love me.
Death is the only way.
I call on you. Please help me.
Eumenides, I offer you my life
to free my son from his destiny.
Silence! I forbid you
to say such a thing.
Hear me, Eumenides.
Listen to my request.
My life is yours.
I am here, Deianira.
I am Polimorfeus, centaur and faun.
Water of these falls,
mist of the valleys.
You have called the Eumenides,
and we have heard you.
Hercules!
Hercules, your strength is useless.
She is mine and I will prevail.
Deianira!
Zeus, I renounce you
as you have renounced me!
Listen, Zeus! I declare war!
I will find Deianira,
even against your will.
I defy all the Gods of Olympus,
and everything that's yours!
Listen to me, God of Vengeance.
For you I descended into Hell,
I battled Cerberus,
and I returned alive.
I gave up my land
to free myself from your curse.
Tell me, where is Deianira. Answer!
It is Hercules who commands you.
If you don't answer me,
then I deny you.
I'll destroy you.
Nothing in Heaven or Earth will stop me.
I no longer fear your vengeance!
Hercules, you have offended the gods,
but I will help you.
Tell me, where is Deianira?
Remember the prophecy.
The day has come, Hercules.
Your descendants will reign over Ecalia,
but the woman you love will die.
Then, Deianira is in Ecalia?
Yes and I will tell you a secret
so you can cross the inviolable walls.
Speak! Speak...
In the forest, in front of the walls,
there's a rock which will open a path.
I don't understand.
The sun has suddenly disappeared.
I don't like it, not at all.
I hate the dark.
If you could see yourself, Eurito.
If your subjects could see you.
The tyrant of Ecalia on his throne,
shaking like a child afraid of the dark.
Don't say that, Tindaro.
I want no more.
Or I'll reduce you to silence.
Eurito, come quickly!
- A monster has appeared.
- What are you saying?
There is a centaur before the wall.
He shouts your name.
Eurito, I know how you hate Hercules.
Here is his wife. She is yours.
You shall be avenged, Polimorfeus.
Avenge me, Eurito. Avenge me!
- You were quick.
- Illo warned me, I lost no time.
I have only a hundred men with me,
but they are the best of Thebes.
They are eager to storm
the inviolable walls of the Cyclops.
These walls are not inviolable
and we will make them fall.
- The gods help us.
- No, Androcles. Not this time.
The gods are against us.
We fight alone.
Double the guard.
Hercules may attempt an assault.
Even if the walls
weren't the work of the Cyclops,
no one could breach them tonight.
The cavalry are
massed before the main gates.
Return to your posts.
It seems to me...
that this throne wavers.
Come, Androcles, with me.
And you Illo, with the Thebans.
We'll find the rock.
Say something, Insult me,
but don't look at me so.
Thea, I love you like a sister.
Forgive me. Can you forgive me?
I know that I tricked you.
But I did it for the love of Eurito.
Here is the rock marked by lightening.
Now I understand
the words of the Sibyl.
The impregnable walls are above us.
Return to the Thebans.
But what will you do?
Are you crazy?
Go. As soon as the walls crumble,
enter the city with your men.
But you, what will happen to you?
I don't know.
If I don't survive, thanks to you,
Deianira et Illo will be saved.
Go now, there's no time to lose.
Go!
Because of me you were tricked,
I deserve my punishment.
Eurito will marry you,
- I will wait only for death.
- Don't touch me! Get out!
I beg you,
just one word of forgiveness.
If you want forgiveness, then
bring me poison before I marry Eurito.
Ismene, get out of here.
Don't be afraid.
You will be happy as my Queen.
It's impossible...
To destroy the walls of Ecalia.
Guards!
Hercules! I knew he wouldn't abandon us.
We'll soon be free.
- I can never be free.
- Don't say that, Alcinoe. You'll see.
My remorse.
Who will free me from my remorse?
No, don't be afraid.
I've come to save you.
Hercules is in Ecalia. I'll take you
to him. Quick, before Eurito arrives.
You are more dangerous than a serpent!
You'll come with me
whether you want to or not.
Don't be afraid.
I want you alive.
Shout all you want.
Call Hercules.
Who'll call. Hercules! Hercules!
Wait!
Tell him! Tell him what you see.
Or would you like a closer look?
- Snakes...
- Did you hear, Hercules?
Snakes.
I know you do not fear them.
You strangled them in your cradle.
But what about your wife?
When the snakes slide along her skin.
Like so.
Take care, Eurito!
No, Hercules,
it's no longer you in charge.
You will bend your knee
and beg for the life of your wife.
Your pride will bend.
On your knees, son of the gods!
On your knees! And beg!
Or is your pride
stronger than your love?
Beg me, beg, Hercules.
Beg me!
I implore you, Eurito.
Don't kill my wife.
- I will give you all that you want.
- No, Hercules.
There is nothing you can give me.
Nothing more than my revenge.
Even my death would be sweet
if your wife accompanied me.
Are you eager to see her die?
I love you, Hercules.
I have loved you so...
From the moment I saw you,
when you saved my life.
And now...
Now I can die for you.
Hercules! Come!
And now my friend,
there's work for you.
Let's do it - hurry up
give it to me - that's it.
Let me do it.
He'll never change.
This time, I'll admit I'm exhausted.
They'll have to finish themselves.
I hope that when
you're tired of ruling Ecalia,
you'll start on a family.
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Hercules! I've got some work for you!
Wait a moment!